Hello,
so today we're going to do a learning
related study.
So we build A and we build an AI agent
that can parse an original learning
material into an interactive learning
experience.
In this experience you can,
you can not only like to see,
you can not only see reading text based
content,
but also 2D animations and interactions
and sometimes even in 3D.
So we won't start today's, we won't start.
We won't use this study to evaluate how
good the system is currently and what are
the things we can improve in the future.
Is that OK?
Yep.
OK, cool.
So next I'm gonna pick a random learning
material.
Yeah, I first I'm gonna send you the URL.
I already sent it to you.
Can you can you open it?
Yep.
It's the quiz.
This one.
Yeah, you can do the quiz 1st.
And then we just we started learning.
Yeah.
So in this quiz, in student name,
actually you can, you can put like member,
not just name, but but also member.
I think so.
Your study ID.
Yeah, your study ID.
Never mind.
I think you can just put your name there.
We can.
We can arrange a study ID later.
Yeah.
Your your tag, your tag.
Name it.
It has to be.
It has not to be your.
It must not be your real name.
Yeah.
Just put your tag there.
All right.
OK.
Next,
you will run this entire quiz whenever
you encounter any question you do not
know or you're not sure about.
Yeah, just like you.
You do not.
You read the answer you have complete.
You're completely clueless.
You have no idea.
Then you just skip it.
Once you finish the entire quiz,
just click the download answer shift and
send it to me.
OK, OK, I got it.
OK.
I actually have no idea about chemistry,
so.
So I think I just leave this question.
That's no problem.
Thank you so much.
Then you can just download the empty
sheet just with your name on it.
Yeah, Yeah,
You can just send this later to me.
OK.
All right.
Yeah, OK.
Thank you so much.
OK,
so next I send you the URL of our
learning website so that you can just
open it.
Yep,
it's saying it's currently in the chat.
Yep, on the left, top left,
there's little folder icon.
This one, yes.
Now you pick the second one,
the chemistry one.
Yep.
Now on the right top,
on the top top right,
there's a little gear icon,
which is a setting.
You can, you can change your,
you can change the font if you want,
change the front if you want.
It's already a large one.
OK.
You can also like use control and the
screwing Yeah,
to adjust the size as you wish.
Yeah.
If once you no problem with anything,
you can just click Start learning Yeah,
make sure you are you are in the first
Yeah,
make sure you are in the 1st chapter
first first section on on the left panel.
OK, Yeah.
Now you can Start learning.
So for how many minutes?
No time limit,
just just whenever you feel you're ready,
you're finished.
Just let me know.
Can you click Start learning,
Start learning where?
Where's the Oh, this one?
Yes.
And just let me briefly introduce.
So on the left hand side,
these are all the chapters and sections
you're going to go through.
And in the middle you can see the
learning content.
Sometimes it's reading,
sometimes it require you to do a mini
quit mini mini follow up quiz.
Sometimes there will be like a 2D
interactions or animation,
sometimes it would be 3D interactions or
realizations.
You can just do whatever you want until
you feel confident about the current
chapter.
OK.
And on the yeah and on the right,
the right, on the right hand side,
you can see there's learning companion.
So whenever you encounter any question
problem, you can just leave.
You can just ask.
Just leave your question there, OK?
OK.
Yep.
Now you can just screw to the top and
start start your learning.
Ready.
Yeah.
OK.
Gary, I had a question.
How do you use this one?
Hello.
Yeah.
What do you mean by far?
I think you just show tips.
Just show tips and go through this one.
All of this.
Yeah,
I think this is a pre generated learning
content, So I would assume any quality.
So if the quality is low,
you can just put a columns in at the end
of the study.
That's fine.
All right.
And how to play this one.
Yeah.
I think you just hit play.
And hello, Hello.
Yeah, yeah, I think you just hit play.
And in the middle,
that's actually instruction.
I think this is that.
Yeah.
You can just click on this and to see how
the structure change.
Yeah,
I think I already clicked the play button,
but there's nothing happened.
Can you click it?
This one?
The ball.
Yeah.
OK, there's probably a buck then,
but that's no problem.
You can just we can just go through it.
We can just.
Yeah, just just go another one.
Hey, Gary,
I think there's a wrong answer here.
Hey, Gary.
Hello.
Yeah, I think there's a OK.
So, yeah, total number is 2.
OK, so there's some.
So you believe the question,
the answer provided by the question is
wrong, right?
Yep.
OK.
Just skip.
Yeah, 'cause yeah.
Mm, hmm.
Thank you.
Thank you for supporting that.
Hey Gary,
I think I finished all the steps.
Nice.
Now you can open the quiz again and just
do everything from the start.
OK, this one, yes.
Oh,
and also in the student name you can add,
you can add one more,
one more synthesize preferences.
Just add one more thing.
Just post, post test.
No post test.
Post test.
Yeah, at the end, at the end.
No, no, no, not coding free.
I mean post test.
Just type this post test.
Just type it.
Yeah, post test, test, Yep, thank you.
And now you can just do it.
Hey, Gary.
I think I finished all the quizzes.
Thank you.
Now you can just download this and later
just send it to me, OK?
OK.
Thank you so much.
Next,
I'm going to send you a question here to
just ask your experience here.
Is it, it's kind of kind of similar stuff,
You just put your feedback there.
OK, thank you.
OK, what is my participation code?
I think that you can just type your name
there or not.
OK, material.
Yeah,
you can just copy the title from the
sample.
Thank you.
Gary,
I haven't used the PDF feature for
uploading.
So, oh,
here let me show you the original PDF so
you don't have to use it because since
this is just like a preliminary,
preliminary usability study,
it's not a formal study.
I sent the the original PDF to you,
so you can just briefly take a look and
just give you our opinions,
suggestions like like for example,
like which one,
which learning experience you think is
better or you prefer?
Yeah, this is the original thing, yeah.
Do I need to write down the reason?
Yes.
OK, you finished.
Wait, I haven't write down the reason yet.
OK.
The second is most frustrated part.
Like what part you think is is not that
good actually.
Yeah, I think 3D is the best part,
but also is the most frustrating part
cause can you write your reasons there?
Yep.
OK, I finished the feedback.
Thank you.
You can download this and send it to me
later.
OK, Can you download this and send it?
Have you download this?
Yeah.
OK, wait a second.
OK, I already send you.
OK, thank you so much.
All right,
so next I'll give you a short interview
and after this we can end the study.
OK.
Yep.
OK,
so I think right now let's let's start
the interview.
OK,
so first question is so in one sentence.
What does this tool do?
So what do you think this is for?
I think it can let teachers to describe
their course ideas in natural language,
and the system can help teachers to
create an interactive learning experience
for students.
Cool.
And how did how did reading and loading
feel like?
Have you ever experienced any lag or
something?
Well,
I think the waiting time was pretty
normal and acceptable and consider
considering the quality of the generated
generated concept,
I think the waiting time was works well.
OK,
so which part do you find that helps the
most?
We have reading, quiz,
interactive 2D or 3D and the entire
workflow and also the learning agent and
why?
Yeah, as I mentioned in the feedback,
I think the 3D helps the most because it
makes the abstract concept easier to
understand and allow students to
experience the situations that aren't
hard to assess in the real life.
Yeah, OK.
So have you, have you,
have you encountered any confusion or
annoying things and where,
where did you feel confused or annoyed?
So I'm,
I'm a little bit confused that well,
the AI truly understand the real real
world rules like chemistry or physical
rules and how can AI represent these
rules accurately on the in the virtual
world.
And I still have some concerns regarding
the reading part 'cause I think there
there's a mostly short experience and the
concepts, so they're easy to read.
But sometimes I feel I might I,
I won't thought deeply enough about these
knowledge.
OK, so you mentioned,
you mentioned like sometimes you're not
it's not feel deeply enough.
Can you illustrate this a little bit,
a little bit more?
Because in the because in the reading
part, there are only a few sentences.
I think it might just two or three
sentence to introduce 1 concept.
So basically there are all,
there are all the definitions of these
concepts.
So I might just spend like 3 minutes to
go through this sentence,
but I think 30 seconds not enough for
student to to accept a totally new
concept.
So I think it's I think we can like it's
10 the like we, we can, we can't, it's 10.
The like the number of number of words in
the reading part and give students more
time and more concept to let them
understand the definitions.
OK, thank you.
And did the course match the topic?
So I also showed you the the PDF at the
end.
So, so how,
how do you think that the course is?
It's matched and yeah,
does does the some part of the of our
course on the website too shallow about
right or too much?
Yeah,
I think the overall level is pretty good
and I think it matched the PDF very well.
Yeah, that's it.
And would you use for the study like for
the website I sent or for teaching
someone else?
Yeah, sure.
Of course.
Yeah, because I think like this,
this platform include H5 and 3D like
these different type of learning method.
And it's a very good new way for learning
and it can explore like many situations
that I can't that I can't access in
normal life.
So I think it's a very good experience
using this tool.
And as a teacher, I think I also, yeah,
I did this, this,
this tool can help me quickly,
like help me to turn my course idea into
a real into a real actual lessons.
So I think I will also use these tools to
teach.
OK,
so if we about to fix only one thing for
the current system we have,
what it what what?
What will that be?
Yeah, I think we can.
I think we can improve the AI tutor
feature because for me and I think
probably many learners that concepts are
easier to understand and remember when
someone explains the explains and
explains the concept step by step.
So I think it's very worthy to improve
the AI tutor feature.
OK, so just one more add on questions,
a follow up question.
So you mentioned the AI tutor helpful
help a lot.
So can you tell me, can you tell us now?
So why do you think the current 1 is not
good enough?
Like or what, what what else?
You you can you could imagine like we
could add to this to the current learning
agents to make it better.
Thank you.
Yeah,
because the currently AI tutor because
because the generated concepts are all
right in in like all all writes in Word.
But some people are more interested in
like sounds or more interesting in videos.
So So personally I prefer the AI that can
can talk to me and to explain these
concepts.
OK,
so you mean you prefer it can just
gradually unbox a complex concept instead
of like giving you everything?
Is that what you mean?
OK, OK,
so another thing I would ask it is if in
the future we also equipped our learning
agents with, for example,
draw you a diagram or generate image or
even generate some 3D or just the
contents like you see in the real lecture
in real time.
But it's but it's in in the learning
agent.
So, So what do you think about this,
for example,
or there could be like another feature,
for example,
when you're exploring the 3D sayings,
you asking your own question to the
learning agent.
The learning agent can in real time just
make some modification to the 3D things.
For example, add memo,
add one more UI panels to help please
explain these things or just generate
some 3D stuff in real time to further
illustrate another 3D stuff.
So So what do you think about these
features?
Oh,
I think a pretty cool feature that it can
help students to explore more things in
in this platform,
like literally everything in the world.
You can just put it into the system and
they can explore,
explore them in the system.
I think it's pretty cool.
All right, thank you so much.
Anything else you want to share or you
want to add?
No, that's all.
Thank you.
All right.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
Thank you.